netspywarescan.com 2009-03-20

# AntiSpyware Pro 2009

Privacy Policy

**What Information We Collection and Why**  
Monolit Center Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to anyone. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the customer?s hard drive containing information about the customer. We use cookies to track how customers got to our site. The information is anonymous. You don?t need to keep cookies on your computer to use our site. 

**Download**  
When you download a piece of software from Monolit Center Ltd, we ask for your e-mail address so we can keep you informed of our new products. By entering your email address, you agree to receive email from us about product updates and special deals. When we release a new product or a new version of any of our software titles, we send a message to all of our registered customers and let them know. If you wish not to receive these messages, you can remove your email address from our list at anytime by clicking here. 

**Purchase**  
We request information from the customer on our order form. Here a customer must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer?s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. 

The ordering of Monolit Center Ltd is processed by third party companies which are responsible for the use of the information they collect. Please consult their privacy statements on their respective websites. 

All credit card information is requested and transmitted securely by these third party companies. We never store any credit card information in our databases. 

**Surveys**  
We occasionally ask for anonymous usage information through random surveys. The surveys allow us to better understand our audience and their interests. The primary purpose of these surveys is to help us in creating products that are of greater interest to our customer base. 

**Sharing**  
Occasionally we will share anonymous demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Forum**  
In order to use the forum, and be part of Monolit Center Ltd online community, the customers have the opportunity to complete the registration form. During registration a customer is required to give his email, and optionally, other contact information. This information is used to contact the customer about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest, and to allow a more intense involvement in Monolit Center Ltd community. It is optional for the customer to provide demographic information, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site and continue to improve the products and services we provide. 

**Special Offers**  
Established customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our customers we present the option to not receive these types of communications. If you wish not to receive these messages, you can remove your email address from our list at anytime by clicking here. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a customer?s personally identifiable information changes , or if a customer no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that customer?s personal data provided to us. This can usually be by contacting customer service. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site so our customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our customers? information. When customers submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
